

Oakland, Bay Area CA http://johnevanofski.net

BIO

John Evanofski is a Bay Area web developer and designer with a diverse technological skillset and a problem solving aptitude. He is also an adept communicator and an experienced technology educator. His goal is to use his skills to bridge the gap between the user and the designer in order to continue the tradition of good design.

EXPERIENCE

WEB & GRAPHIC DESIGN LEAD
Clean LED Energy / Oakland CA / 2014-Present

WEB DESIGNER AND VIDEO TECH SUPPORT SPECIALIST

YogaKula / Berkeley CA / 2012-2014

WORDPRESS TEACHER

AcademyX / San Francisco CA / 2013-Present

SEO CONSULTANT

Branditecture / San Francisco CA / 2013-Present

INDEPENDENT WEB & GRAPHIC DESIGN

David Kerr Designs / Oakland CA / 2012-Present Cindy Cleary Art / 2014

Mission Creek Oakland Festival / Oakland CA / 2013

SJ Sallinger Designs / San Francisco CA / 2013

EXCEL '98 & 2010 TEACHER & TECHNICAL LEAD (Sales Support Coordinator)
Service Source Inc / San Francisco CA / 2009 - 2013

SKILLS

WEB DEV:

- HTML5 & CSS3
- JavaScript
- PHP
- Ruby
- Responsive Web
- WordPress CMS

ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE:

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- InDesign
- Fireworks
- Dreamweaver

OTHER:

- Final Cut Pro
- Ableton Live
- Microsoft Office Suite

EDUCATION

Liberal Arts Humanities (AA)
Digital Art Certificate
City College San Francisco / 2013

Web Design Certificate
AcademyX / 2011

